tabletoptactics.tv 2019-04-01

# PRIVACY & TERMS – Tabletop Tactics

* * *

The following Privacy & Terms policies are in place here for users of our website.

 **PRIVACY**

If you transact business with us either through membership subscription or physical product purchase, **w** **e do not store credit card**   **details nor do we share customer financial information with any 3rd parties.** All transactions are processed through our payment gateway partners, _**PayPal**_ or **_Stripe_**.

When creating a Membership Account or purchasing products from our website, we may collect any personal information that you submit on our website or provide to us in some other manner, including personal information that may be contained in any video, comment or other submission you upload or post to our website. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number. **Visitors to this website are also subject to having some non financial information processed by _Automattic_.** This may be personal information such as an email address, comment or address information for products purchased on our website. For full information on how _**Automattic**_ use and process any information submitted on our website, please refer to their [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy-notice/). **You may request any information held about you by _Automattic_ by contacting them directly here: **[privacypolicyupdates@automattic.com](mailto:privacypolicyupdates@automattic.com)

We may use your personal information to do the following:

  * Deliver the products and services that you have requested or purchased.
  * Manage your account and provide you with customer support.
  * Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content.
  * Communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail or telephone.
  * Verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with contests.
  * Enforce our terms and conditions.

 **As per the General Data Protection Regulation, you are entitled to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold.** You may email your request using the [Contact Form](https://www.tabletoptactics.tv/contact/).

 **COOKIES**

Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites.

We use cookies to help identify your computer so we can tailor your user experience, track shopping basket contents and remember where you are in the order process.

You can disable any cookies already stored on your computer via your web browser, but these may stop our website from functioning properly. Continued use of our website assumes that you are happy to use cookies although you may also opt out of Cookies via our Cookie notice.

 **The following is strictly necessary in the operation of our website.**

This Website Will:

  * Remember what is in your shopping basket
  * Remember where you are in the order process
  * Remember that you are logged in and that your session is secure.  You need to be logged in to complete an order.

The following are not Strictly Necessary, but are required to provide you with the best user experience and also to tell us which pages you find most interesting (anonymously).

 **Functional Cookies**

This Website Will:

  * Track the pages you visit via Google Analytics and or Automattic.

 **Targeting Cookies**

This Website Will:

  * Allow you to share pages with social networks such as Facebook (If available)

 **This website will not**

  * Share any personal information with third parties outside of Automattic.

 **DELIVERY**

Delivery of Membership Subscription is immediate via streaming access to the ‘On Demand’ only content of our website. Delivery of Merchandise and physical products are processed through [Royal Mail](http://www.royalmail.com/).

 **CANCELLATIONS**

By default, all subscriptions are set to automatically renew for the same period of time as the original subscription. You may decline to renew, by cancelling your subscription at any time prior to the commencement of a renewal subscription. Tabletop Tactics reserves the right to deny subscriptions, renewals, and other purchases for any reason.

When a subscription ends, access to the ‘On Demand’ streamed content of the website will cease and the account and its content may be deleted if the subscription is not renewed.

 **REFUNDS**

Users who purchase annual subscriptions have thirty (30) days after their purchase to cancel and receive a full refund. Users who purchase monthly subscriptions have seven (7) days after purchase to cancel and receive a full refund. After the cancelation period ends, all purchases are final and all fees paid are non-refundable.

Purchases of Merchandise and other physical products may be refunded up to thirty (30) days after their purchase, provided they are returned to Tabletop Tactics in their original state. Postage costs for returns are made at the expense of the person or party requesting the refund.

 **COPYRIGHT DISCLAIMER**

The Tabletop Tactics logo and name are a ® Registered Trade Mark and may not be used in personal or commercial projects without express permission. This website is in no way endorsed by Games Workshop Limited. All Rights Reserved to their respective owners.

Privacy & Terms over. Now get back to the frontline and enjoy the content!
